♪ ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN WATCHING YOU ♪
♪ FOR SOME TIME ♪
♪ CAN'T STOP STARING
AT THOSE OCEAN EYES ♪
♪ BURNING CITIES
AND NAPALM SKIES ♪
♪ FIFTEEN FLARES
INSIDE THOSE OCEAN EYES ♪
♪ YOUR OCEAN EYES ♪
♪ NO FAIR ♪
♪ YOU REALLY KNOW HOW
TO MAKE ME CRY ♪
♪ WHEN YOU GIMME THOSE
OCEAN EYES ♪
♪ I'M SCARED ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER FALLEN FROM
QUITE THIS HIGH ♪
♪ FALLIN' INTO YOUR OCEAN EYES ♪
♪ THOSE OCEAN EYES ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN WALKING THROUGH ♪
♪ A WORLD GONE BLIND ♪
♪ CAN'T STOP THINKING
OF YOUR DIAMOND MIND ♪
♪ CAREFUL CREATURE ♪
♪ MADE FRIENDS WITH TIME ♪
♪ HE LEFT HER LONELY ♪
♪ WITH A DIAMOND MIND ♪
♪ AND THOSE OCEAN EYES ♪
♪ NO FAIR ♪
♪ YOU REALLY KNOW HOW
TO MAKE ME CRY ♪
♪ WHEN YOU GIMME
THOSE OCEAN EYES ♪
♪ I'M SCARED ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER FALLEN FROM
QUITE THIS HIGH ♪
♪ FALLIN' INTO YOUR OCEAN EYES ♪
♪ THOSE OCEAN EYES ♪
♪ NO FAIR ♪
♪ YOU REALLY KNOW HOW
TO MAKE ME CRY ♪
♪ WHEN YOU GIMME
THOSE OCEAN EYES ♪
♪ I'M SCARED ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER FALLEN FROM
QUITE THIS HIGH ♪
♪ FALLIN' INTO YOUR OCEAN EYES ♪
♪ THOSE OCEAN EYES ♪